'use strict';

const STORE = [
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "Count it all joy, my brothers, when you meet trials of various kinds."',
		answers: ['James 1', 
		'James 2', 
		'James 3', 
		'James 4'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'James 1'
	},
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "Does a spring pour forth from the same opening both fresh and salt water?"',
		answers: [
		  'James 1', 
		'James 2', 
		'James 3', 
		'James 4'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'James 2'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Which of these are NOT commanded by James?',
		answers: [
		  'Resist the devil', 
		'Grieve and mourn', 
		'Be joyful in the Lord', 
		'Humble yourself'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'Be joyful in the Lord'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "But be doers of the word, and not hearers only, deceiving yourselves."',
		answers: [
		  'James 1', 
		'James 2', 
		'James 3', 
		'James 4'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'James 1'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "What good is it, my brothers, if someone says he has faith but does not have works? Can that faith save him?"',
		answers: [
		  'James 1', 
		'James 2', 
		'James 3', 
		'James 4'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'James 2'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "What is your life? For you are a mist that appears for a little time and then vanishes."',
		answers: [
		  'James 1', 
		  'James 2', 
		  'James 3', 
		  'James 4'
		  ],
		correctAnswer: 'James 4'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "Instead you ought to say, \'If the Lord wills, we will live and do this or that.\'"',
		answers: [
		  'James 2', 
		  'James 3', 
		  'James 4', 
		  'James 5'
		  ],
		correctAnswer: 'James 4'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "But if you show partiality, you are committing sin and are convicted by the law as transgressors."',
		answers: [
		  'James 1', 
		  'James 2', 
		  'James 3', 
		  'James 4'
		  ],
		correctAnswer: 'James 2'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "For whoever keeps the whole law but fails in one point has become guilty of all of it."',
		answers: [
		  'James 2', 
		  'James 3', 
		  'James 4', 
		  'James 5'
		  ],
		correctAnswer: 'James 2'
	}, 
	{
		question: 'Name which chapter this verse is from. "Do not grumble against one another, brothers, so that you may not be judged."',
		answers: [
		  'James 2', 
		  'James 3', 
		  'James 4',
		  'James 5'
		  ],
		correctAnswer: 'James 5'
	}
	];